RG 119, Army and Navy Club of Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
Army and Navy Club records
1892-1936
Connecticut State Library
Army and Navy Club (Hartford, Conn.)
1 cubic foot
The club was formed on November 27, 1879, composed of any soldier or sailor honorably discharged and sponsored by a member, and seems to have limited itself to Civil War veterans. Annual dinner meetings were held, usually in Hartford. It disbanded in 1936.
RG119
1936-007
Historical Note
The club was formed on November 27, 1879, composed of any soldier or sailor honorably discharged and sponsored by a member, and seems to have limited itself to Civil War veterans. Annual dinner meetings were held, usually in Hartford. It disbanded in 1936.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of biographical sketches and obituaries, minutes of annual dinner meetings, membership lists, financial records, programs, secretary’s reports, and correspondence.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Army and Navy Club (Hartford, Conn.)
Subjects:
Army and Navy Club (Hartford, Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Societies, etc; Clubs -- Connecticut -- Hartford
Document Types:
Programs; Financial records; Membership lists; Correspondence; Reports; Minutes
Restrictions on Access
See the policy.
Provenance
The records were brought to the State Library by Henry W. Burrill, Treasurer on August 7, 1936.
Container List
- Records, 1892-1936
  - 1. Biographical sketches (Box 1)
  - 2. Minutes of meetings, 1909-1935; 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 3. Reports of annual meetings, 1914, 1919 (Box 1)
  - 4. List of members, 1925-1932 (Box 1)
  - 5. Treasurer's account book, 1910-1935 (Box 1)
    Includes list of presidents and constitution.
  - 6. Treasurer's reports and receipts, 1892-1936 (Box 1)
  - 7. Obituaries of members (Box 2)
  - 8. Applications for membership (Box 2)
  - 9. Programs and secretary's reports, 1909-1930 (Box 2)
  - 10. Correspondence, 1909-1936 (Box 2)
    - Dues, meetings, etc., 1909-1930; 1 folder (Box 2)
    - Adrian P. Sloan, 1925-1930; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Henry W. Burrill, 1931-1936; 5 folders (Box 2)